http://www.rockmerch.com/pages/privacy-policy

Sign in
Sign up
We've sent you an email with a link to update your password.
A password reset email has been sent to the email address on file for your account, but may take several minutes to show up in your inbox. Please wait at least 10 minutes before attempting another reset.
Email *
Password *
Login
Forgot your password?
No account yet?
Registering for this site allows you to access your order status and history. Just fill in the fields below, and we’ll get a new account set up for you in no time. We will only ask you for information necessary to make the purchase process faster and easier.
Create an Account
Login
Menu
Vinyl
Back
Vinyl
By Artist
Back
By ArtistBest SellersPre-Orders
By Genre
Back
By GenreRockHeavy MetalClassic RockPunk RockAlternativePopCountryRap/Hip-HopR&BEDMJazz/BluesSoundtracksAll Genres
Turntables & Vinyl Accessories
Back
Turntables & Vinyl AccessoriesTurntablesVinyl AccessoriesVinyl Record Bags & Backpacks
By Price
Back
By Price$0 - $20$20 - $40$40+
T-Shirts & Apparel
Back
T-Shirts & Apparel
T-Shirts
Back
T-ShirtsMen's T-ShirtsWomen's T-ShirtsWork Shirts
Hoodies & Jackets
Back
Hoodies & JacketsMen's Hoodies & JacketsWomen's Hoodies & JacketsKid's Hoodies & Jackets
More Apparel
Back
More ApparelBaby & Toddler ApparelBandanasBags & WalletsHats & HeadwearJewelry & KeychainsWristbands
By Genre
Back
By GenreRockHeavy MetalClassic RockPunk RockSoft RockHair MetalAlternativeNew WavePopCountryRap/Hip-HopR&B
Bands & Artists
Back
Bands & Artists
Featured Bands & Artists
Back
Featured Bands & ArtistsPink FloydRolling StonesThe BeatlesGrateful DeadLed ZeppelinAC/DCGuns N RosesKISSJimi HendrixMotley CrueNirvanaDef LeppardMetallicaMore Bands & Artists
By Genre
Back
By GenreRockHeavy MetalClassic RockPunk RockSoft RockHair MetalAlternativeNew WavePopCountryRap/Hip-HopR&BAll Genres
Pop Culture
Back
Pop Culture
Movies & TV
Back
Movies & TVBack To The FutureBaywatchBill And TedBreakfast ClubGodfatherHalloweenHarry PotterJawsKarate KidRockyStar TrekStar WarsAll Movies & TV
Gaming
Back
GamingAce AttorneyAngry BirdsAssassin's CreedBionic CommandoDevil May CryFinal FightGhosts 'n GoblinsMarioMega ManMonster HunterResident EvilStreet FighterAll Gaming
Iconic
Back
IconicAndre The GiantBruce LeeEvel KnievelJohn WayneLucille BallMacho ManMr. TMuhammad AliRedd FoxxAll Iconic
Brands
Back
BrandsChevroletCoca-ColaDum DumsFordHello KittyNASAPezPontiacSmartiesTootsie RollAll Brands
Superheroes
Back
SuperheroesAvengersBatmanCaptain AmericaIron ManJustice LeagueSpider-ManSupergirlSupermanThe FlashThe HulkThorWonder WomanAll Superheroes
More Merch
Back
More Merch
Classics
Back
ClassicsButtonsPatchesStickersMagnetsPosters
Fun
Back
FunDolls & Action FiguresPlaying CardsPuzzles & GamesGuitar PicksMini Guitars
Kitchen & Home
Back
Kitchen & HomeDrinkwarePillows & PillowcasesTowels & Blankets
DealsLogin / Register
Select currency
Select currencyEURUSDGBPAUDCADCNYJPYNZD
Your cart
No products in the cart.
Enable cookies to use the shopping cart
Remove
Scroll for more items
Free Shipping on All Orders Over USD $50
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. This data is held by third parties who have data policies including: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy, https://www.constantcontact.com/legal/privacy-statement, https://www.rackspace.com/information/legal/privacycenter, https://gleam.io/privacy, https://gleam.io/privacy
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, billing address, phone number, or credit card information. Other than your credit card the 3rd parties above retain this information so that we may utilize it to market to you in whatever means are available to us including on other websites such as Google and Facebook, among others. Additionally, we identify you through cookies that are shared with third parties to enable us to market to you on other websites.
Various third party vendors use cookies to serve targeted ads on sites you visit after visiting Rockmerch.com, including potentially ads from Rockmerch.com. Some of our third party vendors allow you to opt out of receiving such ads. For more information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed. Addtionally, we utilize various services to identify you when you return to the site so that we may customize your on site experience and subsequently continue to market to you when you leave the site with banner ads on other sites and emails based on your activity while on the site.
Further, we have enabled Google Analytics to collect information about the nature of our users experience while visiting Rockmerch.com including but not limited to Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. This will enable us to continually improve the services we provide to our customers. However, to opt out of Google Analytics, visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
• To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
• To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
• To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
• To market to you on social media, search engines, and other websites as well as physical mail and phone calls and text messages to the phone numbers provided (this allows us to keep you continually informed and updated regarding product opportunities). If you wish to not have ads shown to you based on your Google account, visit this website: https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated.
• To send periodic emails
The email address you enter into our shopping cart may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc. Further, if you enter your email address to receive any discounts or promotions, you will receive occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information.
These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We may disclose your personally identifiable information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, servicing you, or marketing to you on our behalf so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release any or all personally identifiable information to any entity that may operate the Rockmerch.com Website and/or Business as a third party operator or successor in interest. We may also release your information when we believe release it is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time without notice. We encourage you to revisit the privacy policy page each time you visit for updated information.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at store@rockmerch.com
1
